# **BENJAMIN WOZAK**

126 14 Avenue SW  $\diamond$  Calgary Alberta, Canada  $\diamond$  T2R-OL9 +1 403 383 8294  $\diamond$  benwozak@gmail.com

in LinkedIn ⋄ ♀ GitHub ⋄ ♠ Portfolio

#### **PROFILE**

I am a highly motivated software developer with over five years of experience designing and developing user-interfaces for B2B SaaS products as well as client-facing websites. I specialize in all things JavaScript to create elegant user experiences for complex software solutions. I am seeking an intermediate/senior developer role to work on innovative projects with a collaborative team.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Flipp Advertising Inc.

Nov 2023 - July 2024

Sr. Web Developer

- · Led cross-functional collaboration in agile environment practices, managing multiple projects to meet client specs, deadlines, and ongoing maintenance.
- Designed and built scalable infrastructure from the ground up for an industry-leading NextJS platform, supporting over 50,000 peak users each year.
- · Optimized website performance and SEO, significantly improving load times and search rankings.

## Chata Technologies Inc.

Sept 2019 - Nov 2023

Team Lead/Frontend Software Engineer

- Led two 4-person teams: one developing an internal ML model configuration web app, another creating AutoQL suite with chat interface, dashboard, and notification system.
- Developed 2 API portals and Microsoft Teams extension, serving hundreds of users across multiple SaaS platforms.
- · Spearheaded company-wide TypeScript adoption and group code-reviews through dev guild leadership.

KRD Consulting April 2019 - Nov 2019

Jr. Web Developer

- · Modernized a database management system, integrating custom reporting and form creation tools.
- · Created network visualization tool for enhancing non-profit collaboration.
- · Managed and optimized custom DrupalCMS client site.

## **TECHNICAL STRENGTHS**

Languages TypeScript/JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python, PHP

Frameworks React, NextJS, express/node.js, SASS/tailwind, Vue.js, Laravel

**Tools** Github, BitBucket, Docker **Databases** MySql, Sqlite, Postgres

**Cloud Technologies** AWS, Vercel, Netlify, Laravel Forge

**Industry** Requirements Analysis, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP),

Full-stack REST Development, Monolithic & Microservice Architecture,

**Developer Documentation** 

### **EDUCATION**

Southern Alberta Institute of Technology, Calgary AB

Sept 2017 - May 2019 Overall GPA: 3.5